Finding Aid for Frank E. Robbins reprints, 1910-1951
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Frank E. Robbins reprints 1910-1951
Robbins, Frank Egleston, 1884-1963.
15 items in 1 box
727 DA 2; R633; R425
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The ciollection of Robbins printed materials was assemble form a variety of sources. NO.
No further additions to the collection expected.
The collection is open to research.
Frank E. Robbins was a University of Michigan professor and assistant to the president/
This is a collection of pamphlets and reprints of writings authored by Frank E. Robbins. The individual items were gathered from different sources.
- Pamphlets and reprints
  - Annals of Sherlock Holmes. (Christmas, 1934) (Box 1)
  - Chronology and history in Trollope's Barset and parliamentary novels. (Nineteenth-Century Fiction), March, 1951 (Box 1)
  - The cost to Athens of her second empire. (Classical Philology), October, 1918 (Box 1)
  - The creation story in Ovid Met.i. (Classical Philology), October, 1913 (Box 1)
  - The descendants of Seth Harrison, 1950 (Box 1)
  - Michigan Papyri, III.
    - Mathematical fragments, 143, Euclid, Elements I, Definitions 1-10., third century (Box 1)
    - Astrological fragments, 148, Fragment of an anonymous treatise, plate IV, first century (Box 1)
  - Murder at Manistee. (The Quarterly Review), undated (Box 1)
  - A new astrological treatise: Michigan papyrus no. 1. (Classical Philology), January, 1927 (Box 1)
  - P. Mich. 620: A series of arithmetical problems. (Classical Philology), October, 1929 (Box 1)
  - Philo Vance's New York. (Christmas, 1938) (Box 1)
  - Pickwickian chronology. (Bibliographical Society of America papers), 1924 (Box 1)
  - Posidonius and the sources of Pythagorean arithmology. (Classical Philology), October, 1920 (Box 1)
  - The relation between codices B and F of Pliny's letters. (Classical Philology), October, 1910 (Box 1)
  - Some statistics of Greek verb forms. (The Classical Journal), November 1919 (Box 1)
  - The tradition of Greek arithmology. (Classical Philology), April, 1921 (Box 1)